Your credit based on several factors.
After listening to your story ...
- ... Sorry, your credit is denied. - Rejected?
- You're fooling us! - There must be a mistake.
I have a document that shows my payments smoothly.
I understand, Mr. Vega, but as I said, there are other factors.
You've been on the verge of a credit line is drawn.
Look, Mr. Guillermo Gomez.
My friend Bernie had heart surgery twice for six months.
We have ...
We have 10 recipes for drinking ...
... Every two weeks.
Do not anyone move!
Listen! I want all of them lie down on the floor!
Do not try to do desperate!
And you, old man!
Be careful, Frank.
- Why do you act recklessly? - I'm sorry, Bernie, was not accidental.
Hey, what are you doing?
Because I have to spend $ 199 to make up for this boring recipe.
It was only $ 190, right? Just so you know ...
... The drug is purchased from money pensiunanku!
You just talk to me now that the drug is purchased from pensiunanmu, huh?
No no. Only to turn when someone comes to stir.
- You ungrateful, jerk? - You're a jerk!
You've made a mistake, asshole.
Everybody down!
This is great!
Only by using a chair and a baseball bat ...
Two parents ...
... Managed to thwart the robbery.
Is Bank provides loans as a token of gratitude?
No. But they gave us something else.
Certificates of appreciation.
See, this is cool!
Look at us, pal. Greater than Vin Diesel.
Nonsense!
- Who is it? - Rosario.
- What is he now in Arizona? - Florida.
The, the ... dia ..
- ... He is fine. - I'm sorry, friend.
No, no. Everything is fine.
I'm happy for him.
Rosario had a good job.
Julie get into a good school. I'm happy for them.
- Hello? - You want to avoid me? All Right.
Cursed if you're not the most difficult to find.
Carmen, my love, what happened?
Nothing special, except the fact that I'm getting married!
What?
By Jeffrey. We met six weeks ago.
Approaches such as molasses and pie.
I've never been tied like that, Frank.
This is good news! I can not wait to meet you!
- There is free time this weekend! - Oh yeah?
Yes I Do! I want you to be present in the wedding!
Gather your belongings. Come!
Carmen, very good!
We wanted to come, but ...
I and Bernie now has financial problems.
Shut up, Franklin.
Your basis miser, always a lot of reasons.
Not that forget the goodness of your father, but ...
There are no buts, Vega. Already booked your flight schedule.
Already paid for your vacation.
So, prepare your bags and come here.
Before I came and dragged yourself.
Pal ...
... This garbage does not fit with my stomach.
Why did not want to eat fish on the plane? Throw it!
I'm going to the toilet.
Son of a bitch.
Hello, Miss.
What do you have for dessert?
Still getting used to, I do not have time for a relationship.
But I had time for one night.
- Do you agree with such an experience? - One night ...
... Two nights ... As it should be.
Excuse me, sir.
You should go back to your seat.
This is my new place.
Can I see your ticket?
Come on, let alone me.
It's my pleasure.
Son of a bitch.
The passengers and gentlemen, we will land in Baton Rouge.
The time is now 15:00 and the temperature is 18 degrees.
I forget the smell of the south side.
- Yes I Do! - What is it us?
I do not think there are other names such as Vega in Louisiana.
Gentlemen, my name is Khan. Can I carry your bag?
- I can take it alone. - I insisted.
Hell, you can take my bag.
Please, gentlemen.
We have to get used to.
Oh, come on!
oh crap!
- Give me the bag! - Fuck you!
Did you like it, asshole?
I'll take care of this.
You're quite large in Ventruz.
Okay, okay.
Son of a bitch!
I will kill you!
Nose ... you broke my nose!
- It's your bag, baby. - Thank you.
Have a nice day.
- Her parents live here? - Yes sir.
Finally able to start a party!
- You look great! - Now I have a chance, man.
I no longer singles!
Come on, you'll meet my parents.
Unfortunately, if I know you have a lot of money, I could ask him six months ago.
Mom, dad, I introduced Frank and Bernie.
Welcome, gentlemen. It's nice to meet you.
- Thank you for the welcome. - You're so good-natured.
- The pleasure is ours. - Carmen, say that they are so good.
Calm down, Miss.
Hey, you guys.
Oh God, what's going on!
Kyle and his friends.
Earl, you see? / That's just a scratch. It's okay, he will be fine.
They are friends brother from California. Bernie and Frank.
- Hello? - Do you?
Yes, he's my brother from another mother.
My mother was pregnant with tubes. I think sperm confused.
For me it is the same.
Anyway we love Ronnie!
Welcome and I'll show you to your room.
Gosh, Earl!
- This house seems well organized! - Not so need a big cost.
- How so? - This family of hereditary property.
Heritage house my great-grandfather, because of his service in the war.
As part of the fund negro farmers.
Really nobody knew this house was built.
Mineral resources, including oil,
- ... Make us a millionaire. - Damn!
- Karma which "sucks!" - It is true.
I hope you do not mind sleeping in one room.
We will have a lot of guests and the house is definitely full.
- I do not know you're retired. - Oh, yes ...
I spent some time. Many years ago.
Do not even know who I am.
It seems that everything is here, but if you need anything else ...
- ... Do not hesitate to ask. - I would be sent "chick"?
- After midnight. - Why so late?
Buddy, I want to thank you.
For taking care of my girls, when in LA.
- He was very meaningful to me. - Carmen is very special.
Oh no!
Afternoon workout in one hour, you have to get dressed!
I keep a couple of coats in the closet for you.
I think according to your size.
Let's get there!
- The whole country is here! - You can see it.
Gentlemen, I offer some of the best drinks in Louisiana?
Of course!
Wow, I have never seen a plant drinks.
This is not a plant, lord, this Mid Sprigs.
Really refreshing!
Hope you enjoy!
- Mid Sprigs...
- Kita tos!
As seen in the magazine!
You're the old farts are awesome!
Here it is! I can not leave it for a while without someone seduce.
Oh dear, meet Frank and Bernie.
Jeffreyku Recommend this!
Gentlemen, an honor to meet you. You Frank, right?
- Nice to meet you. - And you, definitely "Green Machine".
Yes, nice to meet you. I said congratulations!
- Thank you sir. - You found an amazing woman!
I know that. I am blessed!
I certainly good in a past life, it was worth it.
Is not that funny?
Jeffrey!
It seems that someone called me.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Dear?
A great guy!
I never felt like it! Make me happy!
What happened to him?
- Sorry, I ask it. - He had an accident in Afghanistan.
- It happened when he save his friend. - I am sorry.
It is okay.
Will I lead the life of a three-meter.
Thanks to everyone for coming. Now I want to make a speech a little.
It's hard for a father to see his daughter grow up ...
... And then give it to a stranger.
Wait!
This is my first wedding speech text.
Here it is! It is hard for a father ...
... To see his daughter grow up ...
... And give it to strangers.
Took it, and then give them back.
But it was quieter when her husband-a man like Jeffrey.
Your mother and I hope you get the best!
- Now we are toast! - Yes I Do.
Unfortunately, I wish you all the best in the world forever!
Always keep happiness, love ...
... And you know the next.
- Leave him! - Shut up!
Bernie!
God, Bernie, help me!
Frank?
Frank!
Damn!
How can you sleep at a time like this?
Where is Carmen?
I'll tell you.
Carmen was kidnapped!
I do not know, I was sleeping ...
... And then some people came and took him.
I only remember up there. Damn, what you do not look for it?
Relax, this is part of the procedure.
You do not understand! They kidnapped my fiance!
Shit. We do not hear anything, while Frank screaming.
- When we arrived, they were gone. - I'm worried about my son!
Can you give evidence?
I do not see much in the dark.
They have a ski mask ...
- They are quite a lot. - How many are they?
- Eight ... ten. Probably more. - How do you not know?
Perhaps because the prison is full.
- They attacked me and nobody helped me! - Now you blame me?
Gentlemen!
It would help us to restore it.
You must find her. The town is small.
239 139 people, exactly, Mr. Vega.
- Maybe a little more. - Sir, I think my job ends here.
We form a team.
Post a surveillance camera.
I do not want to just wait for news wayangku mere child.
I do not care how much money you took out.
You have to restore my son now.
- Now the time is not right. - Someone called about Carmen.
- Did he call? - Yes I Do.
Give me the phone.
Without offering, Mr. Morgan. Five million for your daughter.
You've got 32 hours, waiting for the phone again to meet at the location of the meeting.
If you do not follow my instructions. Your daughter is going to die.
I do not know, maybe. Black money is not good publicity.
Whoever did it, it's all been planned.
What do you feel have enemies? Or could they know you?
Of course, someone constantly makes investing or selling a house.
I do not believe this is happening.
He's my little girl! Must be married on Sunday!
You can help us.
The town is small, there is rarely a crime like this.
And I know that you have experience in LA.
- Not really. - You can help us find him.
- Ny. Morgan, the police have been doing. - They will not do anything!
Their heads are so immersed in the judge that they could not see anything.
We need your help.
I hope you can bring Carmen home!
Hey! Look what I found at the gate.
Buford? Anggota The Rouge Club?
Ronald found at the northern gate.
We may never know. I never liked the club.
We'll check it out. Might be found instructions. Thank you, gentlemen.
You know who did it, right?
I'll tell you something.
This is not Los Angeles.
This Baton Rouge.
We do not work like the way you there.
If you think going to intervene in this case, ..
... Even a little, ..
... I'll lock you up and will not let go.
Enjoy the rest of your day course.
Let us catch this bastard.
片源:涵 聽譯:媛 組幕字點零
Let me be clear, now ...
- ... Without running. - What Are?
Nobody would beat each other.
But I'm not going with the people.
You're so whiny!
We are no longer in LA.
26 hours 32 minutes
Damn chair "bite" my ass!
Destroyed piece by piece.
The good news is that my cock is still here.
Hello, Miss!
Come On.
The last time I saw a bunch of white people amongst blacks.
Bernie, you'd better get out of the routine.
- Meet new people. - But not the kind of people like this.
But on the other hand, my mother told me, I do not really closed.
Hello, master and mistress!
We would like to ask.
Giliranmu, Frank.
I'm looking for Mr. Buford. What any of you who know him?
I know!
Hey, how you doing, buddy?
- We see you're very friendly. - Yes, you look very friendly.
Stay on the floor.
Die, motherfucker!
Now, I ask again!
Where Buford?
I see you do not want it.
Mr. Buford! Nice to meet you.
Why do not you have a VIP card?
- Where is Carmen? - Fuck!
Okay, then.
Ah ... ah ... sit back.
I do not know! I swear!
I had access inside.
Landry's Loft!
- Where was Landry's Loft? - In the city.
7th Street. The place is easy to find.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Ronnie? How are you, friend?
- I'm going to be late. - I understand.
Busy people. Many activities.
I could see.
I ask for your help as a friend. My car was in the garage.
So, can I borrow your car this week. How Do?
My car?
This week ...
... Our brothers will come and I have to pick them up.
Oh yes, I understand.
Listen, you lend your car or I destroy.
You just select.
Hey ... what are you supposed to be somewhere else?
- Yes, we got lost. - Go.
If you do not want to let me go, I do not want anything from you.
So, you want to hold the host?
We take your shoes, let your feet cold.
Listen to me now, weirdo.
If you can get away ... do you think you made a mistake.
Okay, then.
Please take your food.
Old fart damn catch Buford.
- Can you come out for a while? - Yes I Do.
How can you not able to stalk the old fart?
- I do not know what happened. - I told them not to screw up.
20 hours 16 minutes
Why I'm always one to get good seats?
The same reasoning to sit next to a beautiful woman.
What are you talking about? Not all women are beautiful.
Hello, Miss. We want to meet Landry.
- Does he live here? - He does not live here anymore.
So, off you go.
Can you tell us, where can I find it?
- Get rid of your feet from the door. - Come on, lady ...
You do not have to ...
- I thought he would not attack. - Hold On!
Needless to violence, we just want to talk.
We are men who can not hit a woman.
- Now tell us, where Landry! - Fuck!
Let go of me!
Not until you tell me where Landry!
- Where is he? - Working in Bakets.
Place for barbecue outside the city.
Usually there in the morning. Now you get out of here!
Give up so quickly? I thought we could talk.
Besides you kicked me in the ribs.
Nose bleed?
How are you, friend? I'm glad to find you.
Look, Kyle ...
I need 20 bucks.
- I do not have. - I thought you had.
No, really. I do not have.
Give! Before I hit you.
Yes alright.
Why do not you get a job?
- Who are you? - Friends of Ronald.
I think you need to look for work.
You complain to the grandparents, to protect you?
Should not you have someone to take care of you?
I suggest you get out now, before ...
- Kyle! - What Are?
They are the one.
- What Are? - The bank robbery.
- Damn! Wow, we are fans of yours! - Kyle?
- Dad! - What is going on here?
No, just chat with Ronnie and "Bad Asses".
- You know them, right? - Yes, I have ever met.
Ladies.
Your mother wants us to get home before six o'clock. We have to go.
Bye, Bro.
Bye.
I appreciate what you do, but do not make a mess.
I want to avoid violence and threats.
Handle wisely.
There are other ways as a defense.
- Wisdom what do you think? - Yeah right.
I do not mean to offend you. But I'm not a fan of your tactics.
- There is a better way to solve the problem. - Explain to us.
How did you used to be in the military, and now become flabby?
Once you see what I see ...
... I do not want a violent manner.
- Jeffrey! - How are you?
Hello, boys.
- I can not believe this is happening. - We'll take care of it, Jeff.
I can not stop thinking about what causes it.
Calm down, son. Why do not you sleep?
What do you think I could sleep?
What is that?
I am sorry. I through the plant, when parking.
For some reason, maybe you do not like.
Only silence on the case.
I can not say anything of the things that I know.
It seems that the police did not handle the case, right?
Every effort has been deployed to arrest the perpetrators.
- Nonsense! - Sorry?
Boss mocked as a matter of justice.
Listen, Mr. Vega. I fully support your actions.
I suggest not to be confused ...
... Let us do our job, okay.
Julia asked for a pillow fight with Uncle Frank. I hope you're here.
- Can we talk? - Of course.
Sit down.
I want to thank you for your help.
It is okay.
Just give them understanding.
I want you to take it.
It belonged to my father.
Always taken during the war.
Pure titanium. As a talisman lifesavers.
You can see the bullet holes.
- Very nice, but I can not accept it. - Please.
I want to give it to you.
Thank you.
If you can ...
- ... May I ask you something? - Of course.
Do you always ... be a hero?
I Have No Idea.
I wondered what I had something that I had ...
- ... Or not. - Just do it.
Be yourself.
And make the right decision.
What could be stopped ngobrolnya ...
... And sleep?
4 hours 41 minutes
- How many times have you rubbing your nose? - I do not count them.
Habits of the parents of the South.
All Right.
I promise, if I'm out of here, I'm going to Jenny Craig (fitness).
Password?
"Long beard"!
"Moonlight"!
It takes more pepper. Add it.
- All Right. - What do we have here?
Not bad. You can put more peppers. / Thank you.
You mix any here, moron?
Who are you calling stupid, stupid?
- Who are you? - Where is Carmen?
You did not answer my question. Where is Carmen?
I'm going to marry her cousin ...
Damn!
Halo, 1988!
All Right. Who will die first?
You like to go to hell!
Where is Carmen?
- Fuck! - All Right!
No, no!
I'll tell you! Stop It!
In an old building.
I grab my wallet and car.
You'll never forgive you, asshole?
- But the door ...? - Get out of here.
Bring me Harrison.
Enter your goal.
I hope the big bearded man has a will.
I do not know how to get back. / What?
I wrote the wrong address and do not know how to remove it.
Try clicking the "delete".
- Where is the button? - In the "keyboard".
I do not need anymore help.
Thank God, we do not know where we are.
Raise your hand slowly!
- Wait, what? - Shut up and lift up your hands!
See you! Glad to see you guys.
I'll tell you ... this is not the safest place.
Fuck this kid sucks!
Just try it!
What happened?
Come on, they do not want to help us.
Good morning, Mr. Vega.
- Where are you taking us? - It was a surprise.
But I'll tell you, that ... the landscape is very special.
I'll tell you ...
I told you not to interfere, but you do not want to listen.
This time you will suffer the consequences.
Listen, we will give you a last chance.
Do not make me kill you, if it has been completed.
There will be no smoke without fire, bro? Bait is placed ...
- ... And you get caught. - You can not run away.
I'm the chief of police. I upholder of justice!
We will go a long way, gentlemen.
You will find peace in the cemetery.
I hope you enjoy "Bon Voyage".
Fuck you!
24 seconds
- Hello?
- Wait for us at the dock at 6.
Wife who brought the money. Alone.
If we look at other people there ... your daughter will die.
Wait a minute! Hello?
Excuse me, I'm looking for Sheriff Broussard.
- He'll be back in 20 minutes. - I'll wait.
You want to play canasta? (Playing cards)
The three of us.
- I do not know how we get out of here. - Seize their parachutes.
Oh, shit!
- Bernie, are you okay? - It feels very sick.
He needs help, bro!
He had a liver transplant surgery and body rejected it.
If you do not act, he would swallow his tongue!
Oh, shit!
Come on, I need your help!
Good evening, friends.
Great.
- How do I fly? - I have watched "Top Gun" hundreds of times!
We need to understand how to land.
Let's see if there are manual in a drawer.
Glove compartment? This is not your dad's car?
I tried this.
Hey ... hey! Gosh Vega! Do not operate any hasty!
You're a good boy!
We're going to land this plane!
I think you have to raise a little.
I'm not sure at this point.
- It will not work, bro. - I'm going to try a variety of ways!
Frank, try another, may be successful!
- Damn! - Damn!
Damn!
You never learn in school driving! We can not do anything!
Thank you for traveling to Mexico Airlines.
There is no signal!
- What would you do? - I will ask for help!
We are in the middle of nowhere! At least 70 km from the settlement!
- So, you just stay here! - You can not, bro ...
What about what people say about crocodiles and werewolves?
Okay, wait.
Bernie, I do not have time for this nonsense. Do you want to come or stay.
You can not do both!
What is that?
What is this?
No matter whether you're in LA or here, all rushing somewhere.
What do we do now?
Through the roadside.
I saw so many security! How do we get there?
Why are you always whining? Will I worked!
- What are you doing? - I lost my contact lenses.
I found it!
Oh, God ...
Let's go.
Do not move, asshole!
I know you. You're the old fart, right!
- Yes I Do. - We are the one.
You all are amazing!
- Thank you, friends! - I appreciate it.
You have many fans.
Unfortunately, I have to kill you.
- Please? - What Are?
Obliterate you.
- Now, you will die. - Listen ...
You do not need to kill two parents.
I'm sorry, friend. It's my job.
Go to sleep, asshole.
- What happened with wisdom, Earl? - To hell with wisdom.
Let us liberate my daughter!
Do you have any ideas?
Here you are.
How do we know where he is?
I think we found it.
- Any suggestions? - None.
Let's go.
Damn, Earl!
- Okay, it's time, folks! - You know, he punyak many events.
- Dad, what are you doing here? - Are you okay?
We should get going.
We have to go.
Come catch this bastard.
Would you like a bitch?
Very impressive! Drop your weapons.
Drop your weapons!
- What are you doing, Jeffrey? - I know this must be confusing.
Its true that ...
... The plan goes well before you two come.
Jeffrey, if you want to cheat us, should have said from the beginning, ..
... Before my father signed the check.
I always liked humor.
Take his gun.
No one will hurt her unless there is someone who wants to be a hero.
Go to another room.
The Current!
You also go.
Who are you?
You do not intend to marry her, right?
She was a remarkable woman, if the situation is different ... who knows ...
But this is a business opportunity that will be shared with my cousin.
Cousin? Police Chief Broussard?
And.
You're right, Mr. Vega.
Leave my daughter with us. I gave the ransom.
I wish I could trust you.
Unfortunately I do not believe you. We have big plans for Carmen.
Son of a bitch!
Calm down, Earl.
Later they also arrested.
I doubt Mr. Vega.
It's late for everything.
Farewell good.
Lucas!
Let's go.
Oh, damn!
I think I'm going to eat barbecue tonight ...
- ... Sprinkled with mayonaise ... - Oh, this bond is very strong!
Come On! We still have something in this regard.
My hands are tied!
We got stuck. Can not get out of here.
"Let us go then Louisiana!"
"Little getaway to relax!"
- You blame me, right? - Of course your fault!
Can not you just once in charge?
If it were not for you, we would not be here! / Enough!
Can not you at least die in peace?
Sorry, pal.
It's a nice ride.
- Yes it is. - Yes I Do!
- Do you need a ride? - Of course!
Let's go!
I feel embarrassed! You're my white child!
Save our lives!
How did you know we were here?
I Have No Idea! I hid in the trunk.
Remains exactly 22 minutes to arrive, before your mother made the exchange.
22 minutes? From this place at least 45 minutes!
Hit the gas, kid!
They have a team!
- We need help! - Ronald, borrow your phone!
- Jeffrey? - Hello, madam.
I know you would not expect.
Give the money and I will hand over Carmen.
You ... you! Hell, dirty pig!
- Give me the money! - Fuck you.
I admire your courage, but it is not needed here.
I will not give you anything, until you submit Carmen.
As you wish.
Now, I'm going to kick your ass.
Come on dear.
It's you!
Well done, dear!
The little boy saved! Finally, I could see!
Louisiana police finally arrived!
Raise your hands!
Oh gosh! Jeffrey!
How could this happen?
Son of a bitch!
I think it is mine.
Mr. Vega!
You almost managed to mess it all up!
Now, you all must die.
I start with you.
Asshole fucking.
Do not move!
Drop the gun, Broussard!
What are you doing here?
Has ended, drop the gun!
You're dealing with a ...
... Which is much larger. If I were you ...
... I'm going home.
Take away the children.
Drop the gun, Broussard!
Raise your hands! The Current!
Do not act as a brave boy!
We recommend that you retreat!
Because I'm going to shoot him.
Back Off!
Stay back!
You shot me!
- Frank, are you okay? - Yes I Do.
Damn, bag it to save your life, Frank!
This clock!
An hour to save your life.
Hey, "Green Machine" do you have anything in your pocket?
Remains lie, motherfucker!
Yah..kami now want to say goodbye.
Come on, are you sure you will not stay a day longer? / I feel bad!
We would like to, but Bernie had to go to the doctor tomorrow morning.
Okay, then. Give me a hug!
You do not know how I'm very grateful. Many thanks!
- It's okay. - Yes I Do.
Who needs a man when you two?
You are always welcome here!
There are five minutes before you go. Can I talk to you?
Thank you from the bottom of heart.
My son has returned.
Words not enough just to thank you.
But you gave me something else. For the first time in 30 years ...
... 30 years! I feel alive again!
So, I found myself true.
I want to go back to dispense justice in places completely disappeared.
And I want to do with you.
Accept ... as the "Three old fart" ...
... Who kick ass.
Sounds great, Earl, but ...
- ... Bernie has other responsibilities. - Frank, I know about the library.
Bernie has a liquor store. Do not make you stop.
I want to make as easy as possible.
I will pay for the entire operation.
And you will be paid.
You do not have to worry about finances, especially to buy drugs.
Are you serious?
Serious liver transplantation.
What do you think, my friend?
What is ready to "cleanse" the country?
Coming soon ...
...Bad Asses di Bangkok.
Hey, Bernie! You can be more than you are looking for!
I tell you, I loved it.
And me too!
Sorry, sir. You should go back to your seat.
信用額度取決於幾個因素
在聽了你的故事之後...
-...對不起 你的申請失敗 -被拒絕？
-你在耍我們  -肯定是哪裏搞錯了
我有文件能證明我沒有延遲任何付款
我理解的 維加先生 但就如我所說的 決定因素不只一個
您的信用額度是處於最低值得
聽著 吉列莫·戈麥斯先生
我朋友伯尼六個月內進行了兩次心臟手術
我們還...
我們每兩星期...
要喝10種類型的酒...
所有人 不准動！
聽著 所有人給我趴到地上
別想著做些愚蠢的事
而你 老頭
小心點 弗蘭克
-你為什麼這麼不知死活？ -對不起 伯尼 這不是偶然
嘿 你在幹嘛
因為我不得不花199刀來維持這無聊的食譜
只有190刀吧？你知道的...
這些藥是從
你剛才說這些藥是從
不不 別哪壺不開提哪壺
-你不知感恩 混蛋 -你這個混蛋
你犯了大錯了 混蛋
所有人 趴下
真好
只用了一把椅子和球棒...
兩對父母...
想要阻止這場搶劫
銀行是否為了表示謝意才給你們提供貸款？
不是 他們給了我們其他的東西
一份榮譽證書
看 多酷 啊
看看我們 爸爸 這比馮·迪索還贊
放屁
-這是誰 -羅薩裏奧
-他在亞利桑那州幹嘛 -他是在佛羅里達
這..這...
-...他挺好的 -抱歉 兄弟
不 不 一切都挺好的
我為他而高興
羅薩裏奧找到一份好工作了
朱麗進了一所好學校 我為他們高興
-哈羅？ -你想避開我麼 好吧
如果我找到你 我一定會詛咒的
卡門 親愛的 你怎麼了
除了我即將結婚 也沒什麼特別的
什麼？
新郎是傑弗瑞 我們認識了六個星期
但是就像是蜜糖和派般分不開
我從未感受到如此緊密的聯繫 弗蘭克
這是個好消息 我等不及要見你們了
-我們這個星期有空 -真的麼
是的 我們希望你能出席婚禮
收拾你的行李 來吧
卡門 這很好
我們也想去 但...
我和伯尼經濟出了點狀況
閉嘴 弗蘭克
你這吝嗇鬼 總是有很多借口
不要忘了你老爸的好 但是...
沒有但是 維加 我們已經幫你買好機票
這一趟由我們出錢
所以 趕緊收拾你的行李 來吧
在我飛過去 把你抗過來之前
爸爸...
這東西很難吃
在飛機上不想吃魚麼 扔了它
我去趟廁所
混蛋
嘿 小姐
您想吃什麼甜點
我還沒緩過來 也沒時間交朋友
可是我一整晚都有時間耶
-你想試試看麼 -一晚
按理說...兩晚
不好意思 先生
請回您的座位去
這是我的新座位
我能看下您的票麼
好了 讓我一人靜靜
當然
混蛋
各位乘客 我們即將降落巴吞魯日
現在的時間是下午三點 室外溫度是18度
我已經忘了南部的氣味了
-我也是 -我們是誰？
除了路易桑那州的維加 我想不出還能叫什麼名字
先生 我是可汗 我能幫您拿包麼
-我能自己拿 -請讓我為您拿包
見鬼了 那你就拿吧
是的 先生
我們要學著適應
噢 走吧
哦糟糕
-給我袋子 -艸
你喜歡這樣麼 混蛋
我會看好的
你還真是挺大只的
好 好
混蛋
我會殺了你的
鼻子...你打斷我的鼻子
-這是你的袋子 寶貝 -謝謝
祝你愉快
-她的父母住在這？ -是的
終於能開趴了
-你看起來很好 -我現在有一個機會 兄弟
我不再是一個人了
來 見見我的父母
不幸的是 如果我知道你這麼有錢 我肯定早就跟他求婚了
媽 爸 這是弗蘭克和伯尼
歡迎 先生們 很高興見到你們
-謝謝您的邀請 -你真是太好心了
-這是我們的榮幸 -卡門也說他們很好人
冷靜點 小姐
嘿 夥計
哦我的天 發生什麼了
卡爾和他的朋友們
厄爾 看到了麼 這只是抓傷而已 沒事 很快會好的
他們是從加利福尼亞過來的兩兄弟伯尼和弗蘭克
-哈羅 -你是？
是的 他是我同父異母的兄弟
我媽媽去做了試管受孕 我覺得慘的是精子
對我來說都是一樣的
不管怎麼說 我們愛羅尼
歡迎 我帶你們去房間
天哪 厄爾
-這間屋子看來管理得當 -不用花很多錢
-為什麼 -這是我們家的財產
因為我的外祖父曾在軍中服役 所以政府給我們這座房子
作為黑人農民基金會的一部分
沒人知道我們建了這間屋子
礦產資源 包括油
-...讓我們成為了百萬富翁 -該死的
-爛透了的罪惡 -確實
我希望你們不介意在這個房間裏休息
我們的客人太多 客房都滿了
-我不知道你已經退休了 -哦 是的
我已經退休很久了
甚至連自己是誰都快不知道
所有的用品這裏都用 如果你還需要其他什麼東西...
-請告訴我 不用猶豫 -有特殊服務麼
-要午夜過後才有 -為什麼這麼晚
哥們 我想謝謝你
在洛杉磯的時候那麼照顧我女兒
-他對我意義非凡 -卡門是個特別的人
噢不
下午一個小時之內 你必須打扮好
衣櫥有幾件外套
應該合你的尺寸
走吧
-整個城市就在這裏 -你能看得到的
先生們 我能為你們提供一些路易桑那州最好的酒麼
當然
哇 我從沒見過植物飲料
這不是植物 先生 這是仲春
好新鮮
希望你們喜歡
-仲春... -基塔·陶斯
在雜誌上看到過的
你真是太迷人了
我來了 要是沒有某人的勸說 我還脫不開身呢
親愛的 來見見弗蘭克和伯尼
傑弗瑞推薦的
先生們 很榮幸見到你們 弗蘭克 是麼
-很高興見到你 -你一定是「綠色機器」了
是的 很高興見到你 恭喜了
-謝謝 -你擁有了一個完美的女人
我知道 我很幸運
我前世修來的福 太值得了
是不是很有趣
傑弗瑞
有人在喊我
抱歉 先生們
親愛的？
真是個棒小伙
我從未有過這樣的感受 我很開心
他怎麼了
-對不起 是我問的 -他在阿富汗出了意外
-他救他朋友的時候 自己出了事 -對不起
沒事
今後我的生活會只剩下三米麼
謝謝大家的到來 我想作個小小的演講
對於一個父親來說 看著自己的女兒長大
然後嫁給一個陌生人 是一件痛苦的事
等等
錯了 這是我第一次寫的婚禮致辭
啊 這才是！對於一個父親來說
看著自己的女兒長大
然後嫁給一個陌生人 是一件痛苦的事
帶走他們 然後又歸還
當她的丈夫是像傑弗瑞這樣的人 一切又似乎平靜的多
你的媽媽和我希望你得到最好
-讓我們拿起酒杯 -我願意
不幸的是 我希望你們的未來一切順利
永遠快樂 愛情永在
然後 你知道的
-離他遠點 -閉嘴
伯尼
天哪 伯尼 幫幫我
弗蘭克？
該死的
你怎麼能睡成這樣
卡門在哪
我等下告訴你
卡門被綁架了
我不知道 我正在睡覺
有人衝進來 帶走了他
我只記得這些 該死的 你怎麼不把他找回來
放輕鬆 這是計劃的一部分
你不明白 他們綁架了我的未婚妻
該死的 弗蘭克叫喊的時候 我們根本沒聽到
-我們到的時候他們已經走了 -我很擔心我的兒子
你有什麼線索麼
當時太黑了 我看不見
他們帶著滑雪面具
-他們訓練有素 -他們有多少人
-八...十 或是更多 -你怎麼可能不知道
可能是因為當時房間裏太多人了
-他們襲擊我而你們沒一個人出來幫我 -現在反倒來責怪我？
先生
這有助於我們找回她
你必須找到她 這個城市不大
維加先生 準確來說 是239139個人
-可能還要多一旦 -先生 我想我的任務完成了
我們要建一支隊伍
查看監視器
我不想只是在這等著壞消息
我不在乎你花多少錢
你必須把我女兒帶回來
-這不是最佳時間 -有人打電話找卡門
-是他麼 -是的
給我電話
摩根先生 廢話不多說 拿五百萬來換你女兒
給你32小時 我會再電話通知你見面的地點
如果不照我說的做 就等著見你女兒的屍體吧
或許 黑錢不太好見光的吧
不管是誰做的 這都是計劃好的
你有什麼敵人麼 他們知道你的事麼
當然 那些不斷在評估或售賣房子的人
我不敢相信真的發生了這樣的事
她是我的寶貝女 本該在這個星期天結婚
你能幫我們的
這個小城市 很少發生這樣的搶劫案的
而且我知道是曾是個紐約警察
-不完全是 -你能幫我們找到她的
-摩根 紐約警察不是經常接這種案子麼 -他們什麼也不會做
他們如此沉迷在自己的判斷裏 以致他們什麼都看不到
我們需要你的幫助
我希望你能帶卡門回來
嘿 看看我在門口找到什麼
布福德？胭脂俱樂部
雷納德在北門找到的
我們可能永遠不會知道 我一直不喜歡這個俱樂部
我們會查清楚的 可能會發現線索的 謝謝你 先生
你知道是誰做的 是麼
我告訴你
這裏不是洛杉磯
這裏是巴吞魯日
我們的工作方式跟你不同
如果你想插手這個案子
...就算只有一分一毫...
我會把你拷起來 永遠關起來
好好享受你的餘生吧
把這個混蛋抓回來吧
讓我說的清楚點 現在...
-...不要跑 -什麼
不要互相幹架
我不會跟他們走的
你太囉嗦了
我們不再在洛杉磯了
26小時32分
該死的椅子把我屁屁夾住了
把它打成渣
好消息是我的鳥還在
嗨 小姐們
來吧
最後一次看一堆白人在一圈黑人中間
伯尼 你最好別再做這些事了
-見見新朋友啊 -但不是這樣的朋友
換個角度說 我媽媽告訴我 我並不親切待人
哈羅 主人和女主人
我們想問個問題
吉列蘭姆 弗蘭克
我在找布福德先生 你們誰知道他
我知道
嘿 你怎麼樣 兄弟
-我們覺得你很友好 -是的 你看起來很友好
呆在這裏
該死的 混蛋
現在 我再問一遍
布福德在哪
我想你不想要這個吧
布福德先生 很高興見到你
你怎麼不拿張VIP卡呢
-卡門在哪 -艸
好 好
哈 坐回去
我不知道 我發誓
不過我知道
蘭德裏的閣樓在哪裏
-閣樓在哪裏 -在這個城市裏
第七大街 這個地方很容易找
謝謝你的配合
羅尼？你怎麼樣 我的朋友
-我可能會遲點到 -我明白
大忙人 很多活動
我瞭解
我以朋友的身份想請你幫忙 我的車在車庫裏
所以我能借你的車用一個星期麼
我的車？
這個星期...
我哥要來 然後我要去接她
哦是的 我明白
聽著 把車借我 或者是我砸了它
你自己選吧
嘿...你要去哪裏？
-是的 我們走丟了 -好吧
如果你不我走 我不會奢求你什麼東西的
所以 你想成為主人？
我們拿走你的鞋 讓你的腳變冷
聽著 呆子
如果你能跑掉 你會覺得這是個錯誤的選擇麼
好吧
吃點東西吧
老傢伙抓到布福德了
-你能出來一下麼 -好
你怎麼會把老傢伙跟丟了
-我不知道發生了什麼 -我告訴他們別搞砸了
20小時16分
為什麼我總是那個坐在好位置上的人
而且還總是有美女相伴
你在說什麼 不是所有的女人都是漂亮的
哈羅 小姐 我們想見見蘭德裏
-他住在這麼 他已經搬走了
所以 請走吧
你能告訴我們去哪能找到他麼
-把你的臭腳拿開 -說吧 小姐
你不用...
-我覺得他不會攻擊的 -堅持住
沒必要用暴力啦 我們只是想跟你談談而已
我們不是那種會打女人的男人啦
-現在跟我們說吧 蘭德裏在哪
離我遠點
只要你告訴我蘭德裏在哪
-他在哪 -他在貝克斯那裏工作
城外的燒烤店
早上通常在那 現在你們可以走了
這麼快就放棄？我還以為我們能再談談呢
你踢了我的肋骨啊
鼻子流血了？
怎麼樣了 很高興找到你
看 卡爾
我需要20美分
-我沒有 -我以為你有
不 真的 我沒有錢
給我 在我打你之前
好吧
你怎麼不去工作
-你是誰 -羅納德的朋友
我認為你該去找份工作
你向祖父母抱怨 讓他們來保護你？
你難道不需要有人照顧麼
我勸你離開 在...
-卡爾 -什麼
他們是一夥的
-什麼 -銀行搶劫案
-該死的 哇 我們是你的粉絲 -卡爾
-爸爸 -發生什麼事了
沒 只是跟羅尼和「大壞蛋」聊天而已
-你知道他們 是麼 -恩 我見過
女士們
你媽讓我們六點前回到家 我們要走了
拜拜 哥們
拜拜
我很欣賞你所做的 不過別惹出亂子
我不想面臨暴力和威脅
放聰明點
有很多防衛的方法
-你覺得什麼是智慧 -是啊
無意冒犯 但我不讚賞你的戰術
-有更好的方法來解決這個問題 -說說看
你是當過兵的人 現在怎麼變的這麼鬆懈了
如果你跟我見多同樣的風景
我不想表現的暴力
-傑弗瑞 -你怎麼樣
嗨 各位
-我不敢相信這真的發生了 -我們會處理的 傑夫
我一直在想原因是什麼
冷靜點 兄弟 你幹嘛不睡
你覺得我能睡覺？
這是什麼
對不起 停車的時候我走過草地
出於某些你不喜歡的原因
一切都太安靜了
我無法把我知道的那些準確的表達出來
看起來警察沒辦法處理這個案子 是麼
每一步行動都是以抓捕兇手為目的
-放屁 -對不起
你們作為正義的代表 受到了蔑視
聽著 維加先生 我完全支持你的行動
不要疑惑
讓我們專心做事 好麼
朱麗葉想跟弗蘭克叔叔打枕頭戰 我希望你能來
-我們能談談麼 -當然
坐吧
我想感謝你的幫助
沒事
只想讓他們明白而已
我希望你能收下這個
這是我爸爸的
他帶著它上戰場
純鈦 是護身符來著
你還能看到單孔
-很棒 但我不能收下 -請收下吧
我想把它給你
謝謝
如果你能...
-我能問你些事麼 -當然
你是...英雄麼
我不知道
我也想知道我到底是
還是不是 -放手去做吧
做自己
做出正確的選擇
有什麼能阻止？？
和睡意
4小時41分
-你摸鼻子摸了多久了 -我沒數啊
-南部父母的習慣
好吧
我答應 如果我離開這 我會去找傑尼·克拉格
密碼？
「長鬍子」
「月光」
這需要更多胡椒 放多點
-好了 -我們還有什麼
還行 還能再下多點胡椒 謝謝
你把這裏搞亂了 白癡
你在叫誰白癡 你這個白癡
-你是誰 -卡門在哪
你沒回答我的問題 卡門在哪
我就要跟他的侄子結婚了
該死的
哈羅 1988
好吧 誰要先受死
給我下地獄吧
卡門在哪
-艸 -好吧
不 不
我告訴你 停下
她在一座老房子裏
我去拿我的錢包和車
你永遠不會原諒你自己的 混蛋
-這個門... -離開這
帶我去見哈里森
輸入你的目標
我希望這個大鬍子是個好人
要怎麼回退 什麼
我輸入了錯誤的地址 不知道怎麼刪除它
試試點擊「刪除」
-按鈕在哪 -在「鍵盤」上
我不再需要幫助了
謝天謝地 我們都不知道我們在哪了
慢慢舉起你的手
-等等 什麼 -閉嘴 把手舉起來
再見 很高興見到你們
我想跟你說 這不是最安全的地方
這個該死的小孩
試試看
什麼事
來吧 他們不想幫我們
早上好 維加先生
-你要帶我們去哪 -這是驚喜
但是我想說...這風景真是特別呢
我想說...
我已經告訴過你別插手了 但你沒聽
這次你該嘗嘗後果了
聽著 我們會給你最後一次機會
別讓我殺你 如果這已經完成了
無風不起浪 知道麼 哥們 誘餌已經放置好了
-...然後你就被抓了 -你跑不掉的
我是首席警官 我代表著正義
我們有一大段路要走了 先生們
你會在墓地找到安寧的
希望你「旅途愉快」
艸
24秒
-哈羅？ -在第六碼頭等我們
讓你老婆一個人帶著錢來
如果有其他人在場...你就等著給你女兒收屍吧
等等 喂
打擾一下 我在找捨福瑞·布朗薩德
-他20分鐘後回來 -我等他
你想玩牌麼
我們三個一起
-我不知道要怎麼離開這 -沒收他們的降落傘
哦 該死的
-伯尼 你還好麼 -感覺不太好
他需要幫忙 哥們
他做過肝移植手術 現在身體產生排斥
如果你不做點什麼 他會咬斷自己的舌頭的
哦 艸
快來 我需要你的幫忙
晚上好 我的朋友們
很好
-我要怎麼飛 -我看過幾百遍「壯志凌雲」
我們要先想想怎麼降落
看看抽屜裏有沒有操作手冊
儲物箱？這不是你老爸的車
我試過了
嘿...嘿 天啊 維加 別草率行動
你是個好孩子
我們要降落這架飛機
我覺得你要升高一點
我也不太懂
-這行不懂 哥們 -我打算試試別的方法
弗蘭克 試試別的 可能會成功
-該死的 -該死
-該死
你還沒上過駕校 我們什麼都做不了的
感謝達成墨西哥航空
沒有信號了
我們在某個地方的中間 離降落點至少還有70公里
-你要幹什麼 -我想尋求幫助
-你好好呆在哪 -你不能 哥們
如果別人說我們是鱷魚和狼人怎麼辦
好吧 等著
伯尼 我沒時間去處理這件屁事 你只能來 或者是不來
不能兩件事都做
這是什麼
不管你是在洛杉磯或是其他地方 我們都在做著些什麼
我們現在怎麼做
穿過路邊
我看到很多守衛 我們怎麼去那裏
你怎麼總是說不完 我會解決的
-你在做什麼 -我的隱形眼睛掉了
我找到了
哦 我的天
走吧
別動 混蛋
我知道你 你就是那個大傢伙 對吧
-是的 -我們是一夥的
你們實在太驚人了
-謝謝你 兄弟 -我很欣賞
你有很多粉絲
不幸的是 我不得殺了你
-拜託 -什麼
摧毀你
-現在 你就要死了 -聽著...
你根本不需要殺了我們四個
對不起 我的朋友 這是我的工作
長眠吧 混蛋
-你腦子怎麼了 厄爾？ -見鬼的腦子
把我女兒救出來吧
你有方法麼
給你
我們怎麼知道他在哪
我們會找到的
-有問題麼 -沒有
走吧
該死的 厄爾
-好了 時間到了 夥計 -你知道的 他太會惹事了
-老爸 你在這幹嘛 -你還好麼
我們要走了
必須走了
去抓這個混蛋
你會像個婊子一樣麼
真是令人印象深刻 放下你的槍
把槍放下
-你在幹嘛 傑弗瑞 -我知道你肯定想不通
事實是...
...在你倆來之前 計劃進行的很順利
傑弗瑞 如果你想騙我們 應該一開始就跟我們說
在我父親簽那張支票之前
我一直很幽默
把他的槍拿下
沒有人想傷害她 除非某人想成為英雄
去另一個房間
現在！
你也走
你是誰
你根本沒想跟她結婚 對吧
她是個非凡的女人 如果境地不同...誰知道呢...
但這是個能跟我的侄子一起分享的商業機遇
侄子？首席警官布羅薩德？
也是同謀
是的 維加先生
把我女兒還給我 我把贖金給你
我很想相信你
可是我不信你 我們為卡門準備了一個大計劃
混蛋
冷靜 厄爾
他們等下會被逮捕的
我很懷疑啊 維加先生
所有的一切都不會發生
再見了
盧卡斯
我們走
噢 該死的
我今晚想吃燒烤
-...撒上美乃滋 -哦 這個骨頭很強壯
來吧 我們還有一些事沒處理呢
我的手被綁住了
我們被困住了 出不去了
「我們去路易桑那吧」
「去放放鬆」
-你在怪我 是麼 -當然是你的錯
就不能是你的錯麼
如果不是為了你 我們才不會在這裏 夠了
你就不能安靜的走麼
對不起 爸爸
真是愉快的旅程
-是的 -我也覺得
-你想去兜風麼 -當然
走吧
我覺得很尷尬 你是我的孩子啊
我救了你們
你怎麼知道我們在那
我沒有辦法 只能躲在卡車裏
在你媽來交易之前 我們還有22分鐘離開
22分鐘 離開這裏至少要45分鐘吧
大踩油門 孩子
他們有人
-我們需要援助 -羅納德 帶上你的手機
-傑弗瑞？ -哈羅 女士
我知道你肯定想不到
給我錢 然後我給你們卡門
你...你 見鬼 你這骯髒的豬頭
-把錢給我 -艸
我欣賞你的勇氣 但是在這裏派不上用場
你把卡門給我 不然我什麼都不會給你的
如你所想
現在 我要揍扁你
走吧 親愛的
是你
好了 親愛的
終於救了她的 我就知道
路易桑那的警察終於到了
舉起你的手
天哪 傑弗瑞
怎麼能發生這樣的事呢
混蛋
這是我的
維加先生
你幾乎搞砸了這一切
現在 你們都要去死
從你開始
混蛋
別動
放下槍 布羅薩德
你在幹什麼
一切都結束了 把槍放下
你是在跟...
...一個更危險的人玩火 如果我是你...
...我就乖乖回家
把孩子帶走
放下槍 布羅薩德
舉起你的手 現在!
別逞能了
我勸你退下
因為我要殺了他
退後
你射中了我！
-弗蘭克 你還好麼 -恩
該死的 把傷口包紮下 這能救你的命 弗蘭克
這個時鐘
只剩一小時來救你命了
嘿 「綠色機器」 你口袋裏有東西麼
躺著別動 混蛋
呀..卡門現在要跟你們說再見啦
來吧 你確定你不再多留一天？我感覺很糟
我們也想 不過伯尼明天早上要去看醫生
那好吧 抱一個
你不知道我有多感謝你 非常感謝
-別客氣 -我也很感謝
誰需要一個男人？
歡迎你們隨時來這
還剩五分鐘就要走了  我能跟你說句話麼
我全身心的感謝你
我的兒子回來了
我的感謝已無法用言語表達了
你也給了我其他的東西啦 30年來第一次...
30年來 我感覺又活過來了
我找到了真正的自己
我想去正義消失的地方 維持正義
我想跟你一起
好的 就像打人的
「三個老傢伙」
聽起來不錯啊 但是 厄爾...
-伯尼有其他的責任 -弗蘭克 我知道圖書館的事
伯尼有一間白酒店 別讓自己停步
我想做的盡可能簡單點
我會為整場手術買單的
而你也會有收穫的
你不用擔心錢的問題 特別是買藥的錢
你是認真的？
跟手術一樣真
你覺得呢 夥計
什麼時候開始「淨化」城市呢
很快了...
大壞蛋要到曼谷啦
嘿 伯尼 你能成為更好的自己
跟你說哦 我喜歡這樣
我也是
不好意思 先生 請回到您自己的座位上